nudolls.com 2008-12-19

# ND — Privacy Policy

Nudolls.com fully guarantees that none of your personal information, including credit card information or any other personal information, is stored on the Nudolls.com website.

All personal information provided by you during the registration process is automatically transferred to the billing company, Epoch.

Epoch is a professional and reliable billing gateway that serves millions of satisfied customers all over the world.

During the billing process, you will be requested to submit some of your personal information including, but not limited to first and last name, address, and credit card information. This information is necessary to identify you as the authorized cardholder and successfully complete the billing process. Epoch respects its customers’ online privacy and guarantees that no personal information submitted by you will be shared, distributed, published, abused, or misused in any possible way.

You can learn more by reviewing [Epoch’s Privacy Policy](http://epoch.com/privacy.html). Epoch has the right to alter their Privacy Policy at any time. Nudolls.com is not responsible for any changes in Epoch’s Privacy Policy or any other regulations introduced or altered by Epoch.

No adult websites will be listed on your billing statement. Transactions will appear discreetly on your credit card statement as either "Epoch" or "CCBill". Please visit Epoch’s website (www.epoch.com) or CCBill's website (www.ccbill.com) for more information.

The information requested by Nudolls.com includes your nickname, password, and e-mail address.

Nudolls.com will not receive any credit card information directly from you. Credit card information will be sent directly to Epoch and will be used for billing purposes only.

Nudolls.com will never publish, share, distribute, store, or make any other use of any private personal information submitted by you, unless you violate the terms and conditions published on Nudolls.com. If you violate the terms and conditions of the agreement with Nudolls.com, we are fully authorized to use any and all of your personal information necessary to legal action.

Nudolls.com works hard to protect your online privacy and the confidentiality of your personal information. As a member or guest of Nudolls.com you can be sure that your privacy is fully protected.

Nudolls.com has the right to change the above stated Privacy Policy at any time. Please review this page for updates periodically.

[18 U.S.C. 2257 Record-Keeping Requirements Compliance statement](http://nudolls.com/legal/2257.html) • [Webmasters click here](http://webmasters.nudolls.com/?) • Copyright 2007-2008. All rights reserved.
